bloggingqna.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy – Blogging QnA

## **Who we are**

**Our website address is: https://bloggingqna.com**

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

At **[Bloggingqna.com](https://www.bloggingqna.com/)** , we perceive that protection of your own data is vital. Here is data on what sorts of individual data we get and gather when you client visit Bloggingqna.com, and how we defend your data. We never pitch your own data to outsiders. 

### **Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### **Media**

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### **Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### **Affiliate Disclosure Policy**

There is some cost engaged with running this blog which incorporates facilitating, plan, paid apparatuses and substance administrations and so forth. To take care of every one of these expenses, now and again, I used to put some offshoot connects in my blog substance. It implies I will gain a little commission when you purchase an item utilizing my member connect with no extra cost to you. 

We additionally utilize outsider ads on Bloggingqna.com to help our website. A portion of these promoters may utilize innovation, for example, treats and web reference points when they publicize on our website, which will likewise send these sponsors, (for example, Google through the Google Adsense program) data including your IP address, your ISP, the program you used to visit our webpage, and now and again, regardless of whether you have Flash introduced. This is for the most part utilized for geo-focusing on purposes or demonstrating certain promotions in view of particular destinations went by. 

You can be crippled or specifically kill our treats or outsider treats in your program settings, or by overseeing inclinations in projects, for example, Norton Internet Security. Be that as it may, this can influence how you can communicate with our webpage and different sites. This could incorporate the powerlessness to log in to administrations or projects, for example, signing into gatherings or records.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
